{
    "subject": "resource/Dari_(Italian_band)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Dari",
    "human_readable": "The name of Dari (Italian band) is Dari.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9815900921821594,
            "question": "Is Dari an Italian band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7934523820877075,
            "question": "Who are the members of Dari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7108334302902222,
            "question": "What is the name of the Italian band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.708348274230957,
            "question": "Where is Dari from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6709167957305908,
            "question": "What kind of music does Dari play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6116158962249756,
            "question": "When was Dari formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45391467213630676,
            "question": "Are there any famous songs by Dari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42611417174339294,
            "question": "What makes Dari unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32140329480171204,
            "question": "Has Dari won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2438889741897583,
            "question": "Do you know any other Italian bands?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Dari (Italian band) is Dari.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2179_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Dari won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2179_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Dari unique?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2179_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous songs by Dari?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2179_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2179_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2179_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2179_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2179_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2179_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2179_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2179_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2179_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2179_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2179_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention the band's name as \"Dari\" or sometimes stylized as \"dARI\", but not just \"Dari\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided that \"Dari (often stylized as dARI) is an Italian band,\" which supports the statement that the name of Dari (Italian band) is indeed Dari."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the name \"Dari\" was mentioned multiple times as a stylized version of \"dARI\", indicating that the correct spelling or common usage of the band's name is actually \"dARI\".",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}